A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, United States International Affairs Program (USIAP), Urban Poverty, Office Files of John Foster-Bey FA699
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation records, United States International Affairs Program (USIAP), Urban Poverty, Office Files of John Foster-Bey
1972-1990
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation
FA699
1.2 Cubic Feet
Conditions Governing Access note
Material is open for scholarly research, with prior archival review.
Material more than ten years old is open for scholarly research.
Select individual files are restricted, as noted. Permission to access these files must be obtained from the Ford Foundation before scholarly access is permitted.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Ford Foundation archive was deposited at RAC in 2011. Ford Foundation records, correspondence, reports, program files and officers papers were transferred to, and accessioned by, RAC beginning in 2011. Accessions continue as necessary.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
Materials requiring specialized equipment for access (film, audio, video, slides) may be restricted from scholarly research dependent on availability of the applicable equipment. Brittle or damaged items, or materials otherwise in need of preservation care, may be restricted from scholarly research at the discretion of the RAC Head of Archival Services/RAC Head of Reference.
Ford Foundation
- Subject Files, I
  - Bendick and Egan -- Worker Ownership Study, 1989-1990 (Box 1)
  - Chron File, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Economic Development -- Program Development, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Industrial Cooperative Association, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Industrial Cooperative Association -- PRI, 1988-1990 (Box 1)
  - Ladson/Delta Consultancy, 1989 (Box 1)
  - McArthur Foundation -- CED Advisory Group -- Miscellaneous, 1990 (Box 1)
  - McArthur Foundation -- CED Advisory Group --CEDP Advisory Group Meeting, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Membership Organizations, 1988-1989 (Box 1)
  - Minority Business -- North Carolina, 1972-1989 (Box 1)
  - Spanish Speaking Utility Council/California Housing Partnership -- Oakland, Mar 21-25, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Social Investing Study, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Women's Self Employment Project, 1987 (Box 1)
  - Women's Self Employment Project, 1988-1989 (Box 1)
  - Recycling Industry Study, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Youth Employment Business, 1983-1984 (Box 1)